Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Gubernatorial Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1941-1976 (Boxes 128-554, 772-773, Film shelf)
  - Boalt Hall Alumni Association, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 539: 5)
  - Colonel Charles C. Herrick, 1951, 1974 (Box-folder 539: 6)
  - Memoranda from C. E. Newton, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 539: 7)
  - Memoranda from Edward V. Hickey Jr., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 539: 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 539: 9)
  - Clippings, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 539: 10-11)
  - Political, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 540: 1)
  - Public Safety Agency, 1973 (Box-folder 540: 2)
  - Public Safety Council, 1974 (Box-folder 540: 3-5)
  - Public Safety Planning Council, 1974 (Box-folder 540: 6)
  - Reinecke, Edwin, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 540: 7)
  - Reinecke, Edwin, public, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 540: 8)
  - Invitations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 540: 9)
  - Political campaign, 1970 (Box-folder 540: 10)
  - California Journal, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 540: 11-12)
  - Governor's Office, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 541: 1-2)
  - Edward N. Hay and Associates Management Consultants, 1971 (Box-folder 541: 3)
  - Task Force on Public Safety, 1972 (Box-folder 541: 4-5)
  - Employee count, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 541: 6)
  - Economy/commerce, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 541: 7)
  - Education, 1974 (Box-folder 541: 8)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 541: 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 541: 10)
  - Edward Meese, personal, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 541: 11-13)
  - Meese conferences, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 542: 1-3)
  - Meese files, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 542: 4-6)
  - Organization, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 542: 7-8)
  - Political, public, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 542: 9)
  - Political campaign, 1970 (Box-folder 542: 10)
  - Political campaign (cont'd.), 1970 (Box-folder 543: 1)
  - Political campaign, public, 1970 (Box-folder 543: 2)
  - Requests for assistance, mental health and health, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 543: 3)
  - Requests for assistance, legal, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 543: 4)
  - Clippings, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 543: 5-6)
  - Los Angeles Times articles, 1973 (Box-folder 543: 7)
  - Political, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 543: 8)
  - Republican National Convention, Miami Beach, 1972 August 21-23 (Box-folder 543: 9)
  - Republican National Convention, Miami Beach (cont'd.), 1972 August 21-23 (Box-folder 544: 1)
  - Political campaign, 1970 (Box-folder 544: 2)
  - Reinecke, Edwin, public, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 544: 3)
  - Rosters, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 544: 4)
  - Reagan schedule, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 544: 5-10)
  - Reagan schedule (cont'd.), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 545: 1-7)
  - Edwin Meese correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 545: 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 545: 9)
  - California bicentennial, 1969 (Box-folder 545: 10)
  - Organization, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 545: 11)
  - Political campaign, public, 1970 (Box-folder 546: 1-2)
  - Political campaign, 1974 (Box-folder 546: 3-5)
  - Political public, 1974 (Box-folder 546: 6)
  - Reagan, personal, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 546: 7)
  - Alioto, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 546: 8)
  - Boalt Hall Alumni Association, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 546: 9)
  - Alumni Association, 1974 (Box-folder 546: 10)
  - Old Bailey Society, 1971 (Box-folder 546: 11)
  - California Legal Foundation, 1973 (Box-folder 546: 12)
  - California Journal, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 546: 13-14)
  - California State Universities and Colleges, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 546: 15)
  - California State Universities and Colleges, 1973 (Box-folder 547: 1)
  - Clark, William, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 547: 2)
  - Clemency/pardon/extradition, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 547: 3)
  - Community colleges, 1969 (Box-folder 547: 4)
  - Corrections, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 547: 5-6)
  - Breakfast program (J. Sparks), correspondence and forms, 1973 (Box-folder 547: 7)
  - Crittenden Correctional Center Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box-folder 547: 8)
  - Death threats, Reagan, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 547: 9)
  - Drug abuse, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 547: 10)
  - East Bay Land and Cattle Company, 1968 (Box-folder 547: 11)
  - Meese, military, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 547: 12)
  - "Executive Clemency," Edwin Meese article, 1969 (Box-folder 547: 13)
  - Extradition article, "Continuing Education of the Bar,", 1968 (Box-folder 547: 14)
  - Governor's Office, financial data, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 547: 15)
  - Hammer, Lt. Governor John, 1974 (Box-folder 547: 16)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1974 (Box-folder 547: 17)
  - Research, West Inc., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 547: 18)
  - Intelligence reports, Alameda County, 1967 (Box-folder 547: 19)
  - Junior Statesmen, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 547: 20)
  - Law enforcement, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 547: 21)
  - Emergency operations support operations, 1973 (Box-folder 547: 22)
  - Memoranda from C. E. Newton, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 547: 23)
  - Memoranda from Edward V. Hickey Jr., 1970-1974 (Box-folder 547: 24)
  - National dividend plan, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 547: 25)
  - Clippings, Ed Meese, 1956, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 548: 1)
  - Clippings, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 548: 2-3)
  - Nixon, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 548: 4)
  - Federal "Clean Air" Act, 1974 (Box-folder 548: 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, California Rural Legal Assistance, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 548: 6-8)
  - Professional Legal Services Program, 1972 (Box-folder 548: 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, Edwin Meese correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 548: 10)
  - Organization, 1971 (Box-folder 548: 11)
  - Political, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 548: 12)
  - Political, public, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 548: 13-15)
  - Committee for a Greater California, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 548: 16)
  - Political, Friends of Reagan, 1967 (Box-folder 548: 17)
  - Rep. Governor's conference, chaired by Reagan, 1969 (Box-folder 548: 18)
  - Republican National Convention, 1972
    - Miami, 1972 (Box-folder 548: 19)
    - Law enforcement, 1972 (Box-folder 548: 20)
    - General, 1972 (Box-folder 549: 1)
    - Law enforcement, 1972 (Box-folder 549: 2)
  - Political campaign, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 549: 3-5)
  - Security, special security projects, campaign, 1970 (Box-folder 549: 6)
  - Republican State Central Committee, organization meeting, 1971 (Box-folder 549: 7)
  - Political campaign, 1972 (Box-folder 549: 8-9)
  - Twenty-Second Senatorial District, 1972 (Box-folder 549: 10)
  - Political campaign, 1974 (Box-folder 549: 11)
  - Public Utilities Commission Policy, input from private sector, 1973 (Box-folder 549: 12)
  - Prop 1, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 549: 13)
  - Ronald Reagan
    - Discussions, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 549: 14)
    - Briefing memoranda, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 549: 15-16)
    - Correspondence (private), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 549: 17)
    - Schedule, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 549: 18)
    - Recall, 1968 (Box-folder 549: 19)
  - Max Rafferty, 1970 (Box-folder 549: 20)
  - Reinecke, Edwin, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 550: 1)
  - Reinecke, Edwin, public, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 550: 2)
  - Reassignment of functions in lieutenant governor's office, 1971 (Box-folder 550: 3-4)
  - Lieutenant governor's office, 1970 (Box-folder 550: 5)
  - Meese correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 550: 6)
  - Health and Welfare Agency, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 550: 7)
  - Mental health patient inquiries, 1974 (Box-folder 550: 8)
  - Legal affairs, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 550: 9)
  - Richmond civil disturbances, 1968 June 25-29 (Box-folder 550: 10)
  - Notes and work lists, 1973
    - April-June (Box-folder 550: 11)
    - July-September (Box-folder 550: 12)
    - October-December (Box-folder 550: 13)
  - Meese notebook
    - 1973 February-June (Box-folder 550: 14)
    - 1973 June-August (Box-folder 550: 15)
    - 1973 September-December (Box-folder 550: 16)
  - Notes and work lists, 1974
    - 1974 January-June (Box-folder 551: 1-2)
    - 1974 July-December (Box-folder 551: 3)
    - Undated (Box-folder 551: 4-6)
  - Far Eastern trip notes, 1974 (Box-folder 551: 7)
  - Ronald Reagan originals, notes, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 551: 8)
  - Messages and telephone calls
    - 1967-1970 (Box-folder 551: 9-12)
    - 1970-1974 (Box-folder 552: 1-6)
    - Ronald Reagan originals, 1970 (Box-folder 552: 7)
    - Undated (Box-folder 552: 8)
  - Education liaison, 1972 (Box-folder 552: 9)
  - Health and Welfare Agency
    - Department of Corrections, 1972 (Box-folder 552: 10)
    - Department of Youth Authority, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 552: 11)
    - Department of Human Resources Development, 1972 (Box-folder 552: 12)
    - Department of Rehabilitation, 1972 (Box-folder 553: 1)
    - Department of Special Services, 1972 (Box-folder 553: 2)
  - State Department of Social Welfare
    - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 553: 3)
    - Program maintenance proposal, 1972 (Box-folder 553: 4)
    - Program change proposal, 1972 (Box-folder 553: 5)
  - Resource Agency, budget recommendations for 1973-1974 (Box-folder 553: 6-9)
  - Business and Transportation Agency, budget recommendations for 1973-1974 (Box-folder 553: 10-12)
  - General government, budget recommendations for 1973-1974 (Box-folder 553: 13-14)
  - Department of Justice budget, program maintenance, change proposals, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 553: 15)
  - General government, budget recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 554: 1-4)
  - Reagan, Ronald
    - Appointments, 1972, undated (Box-folder 554: 5)
    - State of Israel commendation dinner, 1972 November 1 (Box-folder 554: 6)
    - Legislative Unit, undated (Box-folder 554: 7-8)
    - Governor's Conference on the Economy, 1974 (Box-folder 554: 9)
    - Welfare, 1971 (Box-folder 554: 10)
    - Welfare, federal, material prepared for Reagan, undated (Box-folder 554: 11)
    - Presentation on welfare reform, 1972 February 1 (Box-folder 554: 12)
  - Edwin Meese personal papers
    - "Political Animal,", 1973-1974 (Box-folder 554: 13)
    - "The American Political Report,", 1971-1973 (Box-folder 554: 14-16)
    - Evans-Novak political report, 1974 (Box-folder 554: 17)
  - Sound recordings
    - Index, 148, 1967 December 9 (Box-folder 772: 1-2)
      Two 1/4 inch sound tape reels
    - Peace and Freedom Party speech, Omaha, 1968 (Box-folder 772: 3-4)
      Two 1/4 inch sound tape reels.
    - Staff conferences, 1974 (Box-folder 773: 5-7)
      Three 1/4 inch sound tape reels.
    - Edwin Meese/Gary Hamilton, interview, UC Davis, 1979 February 1 (Box-folder 773: 8-9)
      Two compact sound cassettes.
    - Edwin Meese/Gary Hamilton, interview, UC Davis, 1978 October 17 (Box-folder 773: 10-11)
    - "Alvid,", 1967 (Box-folder 773: 12)
      One 1/4 inch sound tape reel.
    - Dissertation on Vietnam War by Duane Thorin, 1968 (Box-folder 773: 13)
    - Interview with Manuel Val, exhibit H, 1967 (Box-folder 773: 14)
    - Ronald Reagan interview by Bill Myers, 1979 (Box-folder 773: 15)
      One compact sound cassette.
    - Notes on sound recordings, 1967, undated (Box-folder 773: 16)
  - Video recordings (film)
    - "Governor Reagan - Disaster Preparedness,", undated (Film shelf)
      Two 16mm, 100 feet long film reels.
- Presidential Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1975-1991 (Boxes 554-771, 774)
  - Attorney general side-by-side schedules and call lists, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 554: 18)
  - Attorney general side-by-side schedules and call lists (cont'd.), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 555: 1-2)
  - Call lists side-by-side schedules for Meese, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 555: 3-5)
  - Schedules and meetings of Meese, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 555: 6-10)
  - Schedules and meetings of Meese (cont'd.), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 556: 1-3)
  - Schedules, telephone calls, calendars, and itineraries, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 556: 4-8)
  - Cabinet affairs documents, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 557: 1-2)
  - Working copies, Volumes I and II, relevant extracts from confirmation hearings, circa 1984 (Box-folder 557: 3-6)
  - Transcript of proceedings, U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary, confirmation hearings, 1984 March (Box-folder 557: 7-10)
  - Transcript of proceedings, U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary, confirmation hearings (cont'd.), 1984 March (Box-folder 558: 1-4)
  - Senate documents, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 558: 5-9)
    Relates to Meese nomination to attorney general.
  - Package for affirm material, 1985, undated (Box-folder 558: 10)
  - Confirmation materials, 1984 (Box-folder 559: 1)
  - Schedules
    - Bania materials, 1985 (Box-folder 559: 2)
    - 1985 May-June (Box-folder 559: 3-5)
    - 1985 July-August (Box-folder 559: 6-8)
    - 1985 September-December (Box-folder 559: 9-10)
    - 1985 September-December (cont'd.) (Box-folder 560: 1-5)
    - 1987 January-July (Box-folder 560: 6-8)
  - Phone message slips and phone logs, 1985 February - 1987 January (Box-folder 560: 9)
  - Side-by-side schedules, 1985 February - 1986 March (Box-folder 560: 10)
  - Side-by-side schedules (cont'd.), 1985 February - 1986 March (Box-folder 561: 1-2)
  - Phone logs, 1984 January – 1985 June (Box-folder 561: 3-4)
  - Schedules, phone logs, calendars, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 561: 5-7)
  - Attorney general file, Camerena, Ernesto, 1987 (Box-folder 561: 8)
  - Anti-trust information memoranda, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 561: 9-11)
  - Phone logs, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 561: 12)
  - White House, 1988 (Box-folder 562: 1)
  - Domestic Policy Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 562: 2)
  - Acid rain, 1988 (Box-folder 562: 3)
  - Emergency planning operations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 562: 4)
  - Family Working Group, 1988 (Box-folder 562: 5)
  - Criminal Division, 1986 (Box-folder 562: 6)
  - Bureau of Prisons, undated (Box-folder 562: 7)
  - Drug Enforcement Administration, 1987 (Box-folder 562: 8)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 562: 9)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1988 (Box-folder 562: 10)
  - Office of Legal Council, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 562: 11-12)
  - Office of the Solicitor General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 562: 13-14)
  - Office of the Solicitor General, 1987-1988 (Contd.) (Box-folder 563: 1-3)
  - Alphabetical file
    - AIDS, 1988 (Box-folder 563: 4)
    - Alaska natives claim, 1987 (Box-folder 563: 5)
    - American Bar Association, 1988 (Box-folder 563: 6)
    - Argentina mail treaty, United States Postal Service (USPS)/ United States Trade Representative (USTR), 1988 (Box-folder 563: 7)
    - Civil rights, section 1983, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 563: 8-10)
    - Communist-owned banks, 1988 (Box-folder 563: 11)
    - Corrections policy study of the Office of Justice programs, 1988 (Box-folder 563: 12)
    - Day care, 1988 (Box-folder 563: 13)
    - Detroit newspapers (Join Operating Arrangement) JOA, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 563: 14)
    - Detroit newspapers (Join Operating Arrangement) JOA (cont'd.), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 564: 1)
    - Drugs, 1988 (Box-folder 564: 2-5)
    - Drug testing, 1988 (Box-folder 564: 6)
    - Fair housing, 1987 (Box-folder 564: 7)
    - Family, 1988 (Box-folder 564: 8)
    - Financial Times Task Force, Southern District of New York, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 564: 9-10)
    - Financial Markets Working Group, 1988 (Box-folder 564: 11)
    - Defense Procurement Fund, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 564: 12-13)
    - Defense Procurement Fund (cont'd.), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 565: 1)
    - Grove City, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 2)
    - Hate crimes, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 3)
    - Immigration legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 4)
    - Indian Affairs Working Group, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 5)
    - International Criminal Investigative Training Assistance Program (ICITAP), booklet on democracy in Latin America, 1987 (Box-folder 565: 6)
    - Japanese reparations, 1986 (Box-folder 565: 7)
    - Judicial selection, D.C. circuit, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 8)
    - Labor violence, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 565: 9)
    - Lading, Nikolaus (extradition), 1988 (Box-folder 565: 10)
    - Line veto item, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 565: 11)
    - Operation Deadbeat, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 565: 12)
    - Owen, Conan, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 13)
    - Palestine Liberation Organization closing, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 565: 14-16)
    - Polygraph, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 565: 17)
    - Public corruption, McNally v. United States, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 18)
    - Rochon litigation, undated (Box-folder 565: 19)
    - Sentencing guidelines, undated (Box-folder 565: 20)
    - Singapore publications exclusion, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 21)
    - Standing: D.C. Humane Society, 1975, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 22)
    - Teamsters, 1988 (Box-folder 565: 23)
    - Telecommunications industry legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 566: 1)
    - Terrorism, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 566: 2-7)
    - Torture convention, 1988 (Box-folder 566: 8)
    - Trade legislation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 566: 9)
    - Undetectable firearms legislation, 1988 (Box-folder 566: 10)
    - United States Attorney, District of Columbia, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 566: 11)
    - Wiensenthal, Simon, 1988 (Box-folder 566: 12)
  - Iran-Contra Affair, 1985-1987
    Includes slips indicating redacted documents, most likely included before arrival of papers at Hoover Institution Archives.
    - Iran Contra "taint" documents I, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 566: 13)
    - Iran Contra "taint" documents I (cont'd.), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 567: 1-4)
    - Iran Contra "taint" documents II, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 567: 5-10)
    - Edwin Meese testimony
      - 1986 December 17 (Box-folder 567: 11)
      - 1986 December 17 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 568: 1)
      - 1986 December 19 (Box-folder 568: 2)
      - 1987 January 20 (Box-folder 568: 3)
      - Joint Committee, 1987 July 29 (Box-folder 568: 4-7)
      - Joint Committee, 1987 July 28 (Box-folder 568: 8-10)
      - Independent counsel, 1987 July 6 (Box-folder 568: 11)
      - Joint committee deposition, 1987 July 8 (Box-folder 569: 1-3)
      - Draft prepared, undated (Box-folder 569: 4)
    - SAM
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (notes) Iran Departmental, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 569: 5-7)
      - Edwin Meese/SAM: staff meetings, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 569: 8)
      - Inspector general and other reports, notes, and schedules, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 569: 9)
      - Inspector general and other reports, notes, and schedules (cont'd.), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 570: 1-3)
      - Notes/hearings, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 570: 4-6)
      - Preparing joint hearing notes, 1987 (Box-folder 570: 7)
      - Edwin Meese press conference, 1986 December 2 (Box-folder 570: 8)
      - Edwin Meese press conference, London, 1986 December 9 (Box-folder 570: 9)
      - U.S. Senate Committee on Judiciary, 1987 March 4 (Box-folder 570: 10)
      - Edwin Meese press conference, 1987 March 5 (Box-folder 570: 11)
      - U.S. Information Agency, Voice of America, 1987 March 23 (Box-folder 570: 12)
      - Ed Meese and Richard Willard tort reform, 1987 March 26 (Box-folder 570: 13)
      - Ed Meese press conference, 1987 April 6 (Box-folder 570: 14)
    - Ed Meese press conference, 1987 June 8 (Box-folder 571: 1)
    - Statutes and legislative history, 1987 (Box-folder 571: 2)
    - Community Justice Center (CJC) exhibit book, "Senate Select Committee on Secret Military Assistance to Iran and the Nicaraguan Opposition,", 1985-1986 (Box-folder 571: 3-4)
    - Congressional Congress, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 571: 5-7)
    - Office of Legal Counsel opinions, Office of Legal Policy memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 571: 8)
    - Non-Department of Justice legal analysis, 1987 (Box-folder 571: 9)
    - Reagan public statements, 1986 (Box-folder 571: 10)
    - Weekend investigation notes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 571: 11)
    - Major press clippings, 1987 (Box-folder 571: 12)
    - Internal Security Section, Iran, 1986 December (Box-folder 571: 13-15)
    - Miami gunrunning, 1987 (Box-folder 572: 1)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA), 1987 (Box-folder 572: 2)
    - Internal Security Section, Iran, 1986 December (Box-folder 572: 3-4)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 572: 5)
    - U.S. vs. Evans, 1986 (Box-folder 572: 6)
    - Independent reports, 1987 (Box-folder 572: 7)
    - Miscellaneous testimony, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 572: 8-14)
    - Miscellaneous testimony (cont'd.), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 573: 1-12)
    - Joint hearings on the Iran-Contra investigation, Edwin Meese testimony, 1987 July 29 (Box-folder 574: 1-4)
    - Preparation book, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 574: 5-9)
    - Department of Justice legal analysis, 1981, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 574: 10)
    - Department of Justice legal analysis (cont'd.), 1981, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 575: 1)
    - Statutes relating to Iran matters, 1987 (Box-folder 575: 2)
    - Compendium, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 575: 3-6)
    - Steve Matthews reference papers attorney general testimony in Iran-Contra grand jury, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 575: 7)
    - Attorney general's interview with independent counsel re Iran investigation, 1987 July 6 (Box-folder 575: 8)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, photocopies, 1987 September (Box-folder 575: 9-12)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, photocopies (cont'd.), 1987 September (Box-folder 576: 1-10)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, photocopies (cont'd.), 1987 September (Box-folder 577: 1-10)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, photocopies (cont'd.), 1987 September (Box-folder 578: 1-4)
    - Handwritten notes, 1986 November - 1987 September (Box-folder 578: 5-7)
    - Office of the Attorney General, photocopies of handwritten notes, 1982 May 6 - 1987 November 21 (Box-folder 578: 8-10)
    - Attorney general schedules, Office of the Attorney General copy, 1987 September (Box-folder 579: 1-4)
    - Attorney general event schedules, Office of the Attorney General copy, 1987 September (Box-folder 579: 5-6)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, planning calendars, 1987 September (Box-folder 579: 7-10)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, phone logs, 1987 September (Box-folder 579: 11)
    - Iran/Contra discovery request, phone logs (cont'd.), 1987 September (Box-folder 580: 1-5)
    - Attorney general weekly calendars, 1987 September (Box-folder 580: 6-9)
    - Attorney general request for meeting, 1987 September (Box-folder 580: 10)
    - Attorney general request for meeting (cont'd.), 1987 September (Box-folder 581: 1)
    - Miscellaneous schedules, 1987 September (Box-folder 581: 2-3)
    - Attorney general itinerary, meetings, Burns travel, planning schedules, 1987 September (Box-folder 581: 4-6)
    - Request by Pam Naughton, House Select Committee to Investigate Covert Arms Transactions with Iran, 1987 September 28 (Box-folder 581: 7)
    - Transmittal of material to I/C Walsh, schedules and phone logs, 1987 August 31 (Box-folder 581: 8)
    - Office of the Attorney General, exact copy of final transmission to Iran/Contra, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 581: 9-10)
    - Walsh request
      - Phone logs and schedules, West Point phone calls, 1987 October 1-23 (Box-folder 581: 11-12)
      - North, Hakim, FOIA requests, 1987 December 1 (Box-folder 581: 13)
      - North, Hakim, FOIA requests (cont'd.), 1987 December 1 (Box-folder 582: 1-3)
  - Schedule file, scheduling meetings, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 582: 4-6)
  - Meese schedule
    - 1984 February 5-22 (Box-folder 582: 7)
    - 1984 June 26-27 (Box-folder 582: 8)
    - 1984 August 1-16 (Box-folder 582: 9)
    - 1984 August 24-September 11 (Box-folder 582: 10)
    - 1984 December 12 - 1985 February 26 (Box-folder 582: 11)
    - 1985 February 4 (Box-folder 582: 12)
    - 1985 February 27-April 26 (Box-folder 583: 1)
    - 1985 July 3-6 (Box-folder 583: 2)
    - 1985 March 20-July 9 (Box-folder 583: 3)
    - 1985 July 18 - 1986 May 6 (Box-folder 583: 4)
    - 1986 May 7-June 13 (Box-folder 583: 5)
  - Ambassador's Ball, Washington Hilton Hotel, 1985 September 10 (Box-folder 583: 6)
  - Richard Millman, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 583: 7)
  - Meese daily schedules, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 583: 8-11)
    Includes schedule of Ronald Reagan.
  - Schedules, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 583: 12-13)
  - Schedules (cont'd.), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 584: 1-5)
  - Briefing book on the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA), 1984 December (Box-folder 584: 6)